blorge.com 2019-06-02

# Privacy Policy | Technobezz

UPDATED May 20, 2018

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, sign up for our newsletters or contest.

When  registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name , username, password and e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

; To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

; To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

; To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

; To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**

Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive when visiting a Radiometer website. Among other things, cookies help us improve our website and your browsing experience.

Some examples of how we use cookies are as follows: to see which areas and features are most popular, to count visits to our website, to auto-populate forms and deliver tailored content.

Our cookies are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Occasionally, we may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads based on prior visits to the Site. These advertising companies use cookies to anonymously collect data. [ads choices](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) .

They use cookies to personalize content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyze our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information you’ve provided to them or they’ve collected from your use of their services.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Third Party Links**

Links to third-party web sites are provided for convenience only. Technobezz does not endorse nor support the content of third-party links.Technobezz is not responsible for the content of a third-party website. By clicking on a third-party link, you will leave Technobezz website. Privacy and security policies may differ from those practiced by Technobezz .

**About Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We, therefore,will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

contact : chevypowell@technobezz.com
